[
    {
        "cardList": [
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 3,
                "reviewDate": 449825,
                "back": "4",
                "front": "2 + 2",
                "tags": [
                    "Math",
                    "Addition"
                ],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 360
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.36,
                "reviewCount": 2,
                "reviewDate": 449609,
                "back": "1",
                "front": "3 - 2",
                "tags": ["Subtraction"],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 144
            }
        ],
        "title": "Arithmetic"
    },
    {
        "cardList": [
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 0,
                "reviewDate": 0,
                "back": "2",
                "front": "2 x 1",
                "tags": [
                    "Multiplication",
                    "Difficult"
                ],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 0
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 0,
                "reviewDate": 0,
                "back": "2",
                "front": "4 / 2",
                "tags": [
                    "Division",
                    "Difficult"
                ],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 0
            }
        ],
        "title": "Advanced Arithmetic"
    },
    {
        "cardList": [
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 0,
                "reviewDate": 0,
                "back": "Reykjavic",
                "front": "Iceland",
                "tags": ["Northern"],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 0
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 0,
                "reviewDate": 0,
                "back": "Paris",
                "front": "France",
                "tags": ["Western"],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 0
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 0,
                "reviewDate": 0,
                "back": "Helsinki",
                "front": "Finland",
                "tags": ["Northern"],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 0
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 0,
                "reviewDate": 0,
                "back": "Moscow",
                "front": "Russia",
                "tags": ["Eastern"],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 0
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 0,
                "reviewDate": 0,
                "back": "Warsaw",
                "front": "Poland",
                "tags": ["Eastern"],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 0
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 0,
                "reviewDate": 0,
                "back": "Berlin",
                "front": "Germany",
                "tags": ["Western"],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 0
            }
        ],
        "title": "Capital Cities of Europe"
    },
    {
        "cardList": [
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 1,
                "reviewDate": 449490,
                "back": "2",
                "front": "1+1",
                "tags": [
                    "Addition",
                    "Easy"
                ],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 24
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.36,
                "reviewCount": 1,
                "reviewDate": 449490,
                "back": "4",
                "front": "2+2",
                "tags": [
                    "Addition",
                    "Easy"
                ],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 24
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 1,
                "reviewDate": 449490,
                "back": "2",
                "front": "4 / 2",
                "tags": [
                    "Division",
                    "Difficult"
                ],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 24
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.6,
                "reviewCount": 1,
                "reviewDate": 449490,
                "back": "1",
                "front": "5 / 5",
                "tags": [
                    "Division",
                    "Easy"
                ],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 24
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.5,
                "reviewCount": 1,
                "reviewDate": 449490,
                "back": "4",
                "front": "12 / 3",
                "tags": [
                    "Division",
                    "Difficult"
                ],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 24
            },
            {
                "ease": 2.36,
                "reviewCount": 1,
                "reviewDate": 449490,
                "back": "8",
                "front": "4 + 4",
                "tags": [
                    "Addition",
                    "Easy"
                ],
                "status": 0,
                "currentInterval": 24
            }
        ],
        "title": "Math"
    }
]